articleswrap.com 2016-11-05

# ArticlesWrap Policy – Point to Accompany While Submitting Article

Your privacy is very important to us and it is our responsibility to protect the data you provide to us in normal circumstances. This Privacy Policy provides you the explanation on how Articleswrap collects, uses, and discloses the personal information offered by you as a result of the use of Articleswrap.com. We hope that our complete privacy policy below will help you to better understand what data we collect and how we use it.

Information Collection and Use:-  
•     Articleswrap collects personal information such as your name, email address, etc. When you register for author account.  
•    We use this information in order to contact you and offer you further information about our company and services.  
•    We may use the personal information you provided to give the services you requested and for our own research and analysis to improve on the services and products that we deliver, as well as develop new services and products.  
•    We may distribute this information with our authorized partners and/or with third parties who act for or on behalf of us, but we do not otherwise provide or sell any information gathered on this Site to outside vendors.  
Information Sharing and Disclosure:-  
•    Your contact information is never released or sold to any vendor, partner or outside agency. Articleswrap, however, reserves the right to contact Articleswrap members via email as deem compulsory.  
•    The Articleswrap has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.  
•    You can reject to submit personal information for any of our services, in which case Articleswrap may not be able to provide services to you.

Legal Disclaimer:-  
Though we make efforts to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is compulsory in order to conform to the decree of the law or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

Change in Privacy Policy:-  
Articleswrap may revise the privacy policy from time to time. Readers are encouraged to check the policy from time to time, however, if significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, we will post an important announcement on our site notifying you of the change.
